puravankara.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy

Puravankara Projects Ltd. (as used herein, the name "Puravankara" includes Puravankara Projects Ltd. and all companies wholly or partially owned by it) makes every effort to treat your personal information as safely and securely as reasonably possible.

Please read the following privacy policy to better understand how your personal information may be collected and used as you access various areas of our website.

As described below, your information may be collected by Puravankara, disclosed to third parties, and used by third parties and Puravankara. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you and how we may use that information. Some of the reasons why we collect your personal information include:

  * to register you so that you access certain parts of the Puravankara site;
  * to register you so that you may subscribe to our newsletters;
  * * so that you may participate in discussion forums on our site; and
  * provide you with a more personalized and meaningful experience on the Puravankara site

We occasionally employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. For example, other companies and individuals may fulfill your orders from us, send you postal mail and e-maill, remove repetitive information from our customer lists, analyze our data, provide us with marketing assistance, and process credit card payments. These third party service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We do not sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes. We do not intend to disclose any personal information of yours without your consent to any third party who is not bound to act on our behalf unless such disclosure is required by law.
